JORGE ALIAGA LUQUE

INDUSTRIAL ELECTRONICS AND AUTOMATION ENGINEER Madrid, Spain

+34 674 745 883

jorgealiaga36@gmail.com

Jorge Aliaga Luque



Hard-working and decisive person with experience in software development through participation in electronic defence projects. Strong interest in Data Science and machine learning, with a desire to train in this field at a professional level.

KNOWLEDGE

- C
- C++
- Python (Scikit-learn, NumPy, Pandas, , Matplotlib, Seaborn)
- TensorFlow
- Keras

- Jupyter Notebook
- MATLAB
- Git / Github
- Linux

LANGUAGES

· SPANISH

(Mother tongue)

· ENGLISH

(B2)

WORKING EXPERIENCE

JUNIOR ENGINEER OCT 2021 -CURRENT

INDRA SISTEMAS

- Training in artificial intelligence algorithms for different EOIR (Electro-Optical/Infrared) systems for the FCAS defence project.
- Analysis and testing of different MATLAB toolboxes related to computer vision applicable to the FCAS defence project.
- Resolution of incidents in embedded software in the IRST F-110 defence project.
- Customer training on maintenance tasks in the REGULUS defence project.

PROGRAMMER

MAR 2021 - APR 2021

DEUSER

- · Programming of PLC's in TIA Portal (Siemens).
- · KUKA robotics programming via WorkVisual.

EDUCATION

ERASMUS + PROGRAMME

SEP 2020 - FEB 2021

BUDAPEST UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY AND ECONOMICS

BACHELOR'S IN INDUSTRIAL ELECTRONICS AND AUTOMATION

2016 - 2021

CARLOS III UNIVERSITY OF MADRID

Knowledge of control engineering, modelling of continuous and discrete systems with SFC and LD, robotics programming with RAPID and home automation using KNX.

COURSES

DEEP LEARNING SPECIALIZATION

Coursera (160h)

Theoretical and practical knowledge of neural networks such as CNNs, RNNs or LSTMs as well as strategies for their improvement (Regularisation/Optimisation). Implementation in Python, TensorFlow and Keras.

OPTOLECTRONICS AND APPLICATIONS

UNIVERSITY OF ALCALÁ (MADRID)